// our question array is an array of quwstion object where each object has a question, options
//right answer and points
export const quesArray = [
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
    options: ["Virtual DOM", "Original DOM", "Both A and B", "None of these"],
    correctAns: 0,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "What is ReactJS?",
    options: [
      "Server side framework",
      "User interface framework",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAns: 1,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Identify the one which is used to pass data to components from outside.",
    options: ["Render with arguments", "setSate", "ProtoTypes", "Props"],
    correctAns: 3,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "Who created React.js?",
    options: ["Jordan Mike", "Jordan Walke", "Tim Lee", "Jordan Lee"],
    correctAns: 2,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Babel?",
    options: [
      "JavaScript Compiler",
      "JavaScript Interpreter",
      "JavaScript Transpiler",
      "JavaScript Garbage Collector",
    ],
    correctAns: 0,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "In which language is React.js written?",
    options: ["Python", "Javascript", "C++", "Java"],
    correctAns: 1,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "Identify the command used to create a react app.",
    options: [
      "npm install create-react-app",
      "npm install -g create-react-app",
      "install -g create-react-app",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAns: 1,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
    options: ["3000", "3306", "3030", "8080"],
    correctAns: 4,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "How many elements can a valid react component return?",
    options: ["1", "5", "3", "4"],
    correctAns: 0,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question:
      "State whether true or false:  Props are methods into other components?",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    correctAns: 0,
    points: 10,
  },
  {
    question: "A state in React.js is also known as?",
    options: [
      "Extrenal storage of a component",
      "Internal storage of a component",
      "Permanent Storage",
      "All of the above",
    ],
    correctAns: 1,
    points: 10,
  },
];
